{
    "id": "5a0e755d65ba4426a6a197d2a1cbfa14",
    "title": "Tenses Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I realized that we ………………… before.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "have met",
                "had met"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "When I arrived at the party, Jane …………………. home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "already went",
                "has already gone",
                "had already gone"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I wondered who …………………. the door open.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "has left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "For over 900 years, the castle ………………… on the hill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stands",
                "is standing",
                "has stood"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I thought I ....................................... the parcel a week before.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sent",
                "would sent",
                "had sent"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had gone to university, I …………………. law.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will study",
                "would study",
                "would have studied"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "As soon as I had put the phone down it ………………… rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ring",
                "rang",
                "rung"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When I got there the house ………………….. down.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was pulled",
                "has been pulled",
                "had been pulled"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It ………………….. since last Saturday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is raining",
                "has been raining",
                "was raining"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you …………………. he would have come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "asked",
                "have asked",
                "had asked"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}